<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[ETFN Fortnite News]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fortnite Leaks News and more. The world's largest Fortnite database and mobile-friendly website. ]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/jgr08og945vn934-4cvv9732c92hgbv321</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:28:04 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.etfn.dev/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[How To Redeem Purchase When Reloading V-Bucks ]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here's how to redeem v-bucks or other items purchased with the new "Store page on etfn.dev" Shortcuts: 1) How to redeem V-Bucks or items...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/how-to-redeem-purchase-when-reloading-v-bucks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63a3adda6d234791aa4c7ab8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 01:19:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_ce74a62246da4cdea2727a214942270c~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here's how to redeem v-bucks or other items purchased with the new "Store page on etfn.dev"</p>

<p>Shortcuts: </p>
<p><u>1) How to redeem V-Bucks or items</u></p>
<p><u>2) How to redeem V-Bucks or items on Switch</u> </p>
<p><u>3) My account was charged but I never received my item after following steps 1 or 2</u> </p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_ce74a62246da4cdea2727a214942270c~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3><u>1) How to redeem V-Bucks or items</u></h3><p>To claim your items, you must relaunch your game. If the v-bucks or whatever item you purchased doesn't appear instantly in your account please check your Epic Games purchase history <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/account/transactions" target="_blank" ><u>here</u></a> and confirm that you bought the item and it went through. NOTE: You will likely not get a popup or reward screen but you should still receive the item.</p>
<h3><u>2) How to redeem V-Bucks on Switch</u></h3><p>On switch, you cannot redeem your items. Please log onto a different platform to redeem these items </p>

<p><u>My account was charged but I never received my item after following steps 1 or 2</u></p>
<p>If your bank account was charged and you followed the first 2 steps, go here to check your <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/account/transactions" target="_blank" ><u>epic games purchase history</u></a>. If it doesn't show any recently purchased items the charge made to your bank account should be dropped, if a purchase was shown and you did both steps, contact the epics support team to assist you with the issue. </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RICARICA V-BUCK]]></title><description><![CDATA[Da Il team di Fortnite Fortnite sta testando una nuova funzionalità di ricarica dei V-buck Stiamo sperimentando una nuova funzionalità...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/ricarica-v-buck</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63a23b96c17f195d634bf18e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 22:47:52 GMT</pubDate><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Da Il team di Fortnite</p>
<p>Fortnite sta testando una nuova funzionalità di ricarica dei V-buck
Stiamo sperimentando una nuova funzionalità per i V-buck. Per la durata del test, alcuni giocatori in Italia e in Germania vedranno comparire un'opzione "Ricarica V-buck" nel Negozio oggetti quando effettuano un acquisto.

​Se fai parte dei giocatori che partecipano al test, la Ricarica dei V-buck è disponibile quando si visualizza un'offerta nel Negozio oggetti. Se i tuoi V-buck non sono sufficienti per acquistare un oggetto, l'opzione di ricarica V-buck comparirà mentre lo controlli. In questo modo potrai acquistare V-buck senza lasciare l'oggetto guardato.

I giocatori italiani e tedeschi potrebbero trovare delle altre offerte di V-buck durante la ricarica. Queste offerte sono suddivise in incrementi di 100 V-buck e vanno da 100 V-buck a 2000 V-buck. Il loro prezzo è allineato alle offerte di V-buck esistenti, ma consentono di acquistare quantità diverse di V-buck per volta. I pacchetti di V-buck già esistenti rimarranno disponibili per tutti i giocatori.


COSA NE SARÀ DELLA RICARICA DI V-BUCK IN FUTURO? 
In funzione dei risultati del test, potremmo estendere il test ad altri giocatori in futuro.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How To Reload V-Bucks]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here's how to reload v-bucks on etfn.dev! 1) Select an option First, select one of the available options here. You will be redirected to...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/how-to-reload-v-bucks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63a2056c033808b459530fbf</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2022 19:02:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f8379b9727614b44a9be4498d50725d3~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here's how to reload v-bucks on etfn.dev!</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f8379b9727614b44a9be4498d50725d3~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>1) Select an option</h3><p>First, select one of the available options <a href="https://etfn.dev/v-bucks" target="_blank" ><u>here</u></a>. You will be redirected to <a href="epicgames.com" target="_blank" ><u>epicgames.com</u></a><u>.</u></p>
<h3>2) Sign in to your Epic Games Account</h3><p>After being redirected, you may be asked to sign into epic games. Make sure your signed into the account that's connected to your Fortnite account (This should already be completed). This will provide a secure and instant connection whenever purchasing items</p>
<h3>3) Enter your information</h3><p>Enter information for the card you're using to purchase the item. This information is kept secure in the Epic Games database and will not be saved</p>
<h3>5) Purchase</h3><p>Once all payment information has been filled out, select purchase. Once you purchase your item, open Fortnite and you should receive your v-bucks</p>
<h3>Is this safe?</h3><p>Yes, etfn.dev is only providing links to the official Epic Games website. It provides links to specific v-buck purchase amounts that arent available through <a href="fortnite.com" target="_blank" ><u>fortnite.com</u></a> or <a href="epicgames.com/store" target="_blank" ><u>epicgames.com/store</u></a><u>.</u></p>

<p>Because its an epic games official website, etfn.dev is not responsible for any issues that may occur during checkout. This method is completely safe and secure</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[All Fortnite Creative 2.0 Leaks]]></title><description><![CDATA[CREATIVE 2.0 INFO @FNBRCreate - Twitter CONFIRMED Creative 2.0 will officially release in late 2022 (With possible delays) Creative 1.0...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/all-fortnite-creative-2-0-leaks</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62f9b8af26980b748cffa50d</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 03:54:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_9400de0dd6864fa18cef413d86991be8~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<hr><h2>CREATIVE 2.0 INFO </h2><p><strong>@FNBRCreate - Twitter</strong></p><hr><h3>CONFIRMED</h3><ul>
  <li>Creative 2.0 will officially release in late 2022 (With possible delays)</li>
  <li>Creative 1.0 and 2.0 will work at the same time (EX: One person on a PC using 2.0 while a person on a console uses 1.0)</li>
  <li>Scripting will at some point become available to <strong>ALL platforms</strong></li>
  <li>2.0 features will be “Dumbed down” into 1.0 devices whenever possible</li>
  <li>2.0 will contain basic UE4/5 tools such as terrain editors, Cameras, Live Changes, etc.</li>
  <li>Creative 2.0 will be more “Open” meaning anyone that submits a map with having to go through a REVIEW phase before the map is fully released</li>
  <li>From the start, it will be more limited while developers work hard to release additional features</li>
</ul><h3>VERSE (Scripting/Coding) LEAKS</h3><ul>
  <li>Math calculations and algorithms (Basic Level) <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Score device)</strong></li>
  <li>Debugging <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Logging to the screen or to a file <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Ability to create or destroy objects <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Prop Manager)</strong></li>
  <li>Spawn entities (similar to how actors spawn in Unreal Engine) <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Level streaming <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Control in-game physics via speed, vectors, and velocity <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Physics Devices)</strong></li>
  <li>Add and operate particle systems <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: VFX creator)</strong></li>
  <li>Control audio, lights, gravity <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Lighting Device, Radio/Sound FX, Settings)</strong></li>
  <li>Modify objects to change their appearance, composition, and animations <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Prop manager)</strong></li>
  <li>Play animations <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Mesh Animator & N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Add, alter, or remove gameplay tags <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Teleportation device <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Throwable teleporters – UNRELEASED)</strong></li>
  <li>A device (timer) to start, save, load, pause, and resume <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Timer Device, Save Point)</strong></li>
  <li>Vehicle spawner (Any vehicle) <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Vehicle spawn pads)</strong></li>
  <li>Vending machine to spawn items <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Vending Machine)</strong></li>
  <li>Script device <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Script Device – UNRELEASED)</strong></li>
  <li>Control arrays and data types <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: idk)</strong></li>
  <li>Operate UI elements <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Hud Controller)</strong></li>
  <li>Bind and map actions <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Creature spawner manager <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Capture Spawner)</strong></li>
  <li>Decide what actions take place when a player looks away from another user or device <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Focus device/Settings - UNRELEASED)</strong></li>
  <li>Sentry device to track players <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: N/A)</strong></li>
  <li>Player spawner <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Spawn pads/Checkpoint/SkySpawn)</strong></li>
  <li>Control over player inventories and their weapons <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Item Granter/ Remover – SETTINGS)</strong></li>
  <li>Custom HUDs <strong>(UI Elements, 1.0 Equivalent: Hud controller)</strong></li>
  <li>Scoreboard control <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Scoreboard)</strong></li>
  <li>Add NPCs and control their actions such as emotes and dialog <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Guard Device)</strong></li>
  <li>Control over building <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: BuildMode Settings)</strong></li>
  <li>Live team and player stats <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Lots of stuff)</strong></li>
  <li>Create custom models <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Mesh Animator)</strong></li>
  <li>Item spawner <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Item Spawner)</strong></li>
  <li>Storm controller <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: If </strong>I<strong> have to tell you then you should visit the doctor)</strong></li>
  <li>AI scripting <strong>(1.0 Equivalent: Script Device – UNRELEASED)</strong></li>
</ul><h3>CREATORS - LEAKS</h3><ul>
  <li>A new system for how content creators are evaluated and how their maps are featured</li>
  <li>Publishing rights to a larger audience of players</li>
  <li>Selling/Buying (Marketplace) creations</li>
  <li>Before publishing, there will be a review period that hasn't been used before</li>
  <li>Before submitting to discovery a MUCH larger review period and more restrictions will be set. (THIS AFFECTS the live edits feature)</li>
  <li>At the start, it will be CHAOTIC so reviews will likely take longer and be more strict and over time once most features are released, the reviewing system will ease up.</li>
</ul><h3>RUMORS </h3><ul>
  <li>2.0 Is likely to release during the fall of this year</li>
  <li>2.0 will be another application and not intertwined with the original Fortnite</li>
</ul><hr><h2>In-Depth</h2><p>A look at how the Terrain Editor is likely to work and look. (This video is a demonstration of the Chapter 2 island being built in UE4</p>
<a href="https://video.wixstatic.com/video/ee6e59_2f9bd9c6dad94c5995ff93b97c903982/360p/mp4/file.mp4">https://video.wixstatic.com/video/ee6e59_2f9bd9c6dad94c5995ff93b97c903982/360p/mp4/file.mp4</a>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f6cf49864dda451b83f472f49dc8296c~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_894,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fortnite X Dragon Ball Z Arrives Soon...]]></title><description><![CDATA[Being one of the most hyped-up collabs for the past few months, Fortnite x Dragon Ball Z is about to arrive next update (v21.40) The...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/fortnite-x-dragon-ball-zarrives-soon</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62f5d4d946e1fd2b336b102d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 04:25:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_8d87fb1d45eb4a03a5cc2d23a64d51bf~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Being one of the most hyped-up collabs for the past few months, Fortnite x Dragon Ball Z is about to arrive next update (v21.40)</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_8d87fb1d45eb4a03a5cc2d23a64d51bf~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>The Arrival Date\</h3><p>Fortnite X Dragon Ball Z officially starts Tuesday, August 16th. Update v21.40 will hold all the content for this collab so more leaks will arrive once downtime has begun.</p>
<h3>Current Leaks</h3><p>This will be updated shortly</p> ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grappler Gloves Are Here! Where to Find Them and How to Use Them]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Grappler Gloves are finally here! Here's where to find them and how to use them. ]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/grappler-gloves-are-here-where-to-find-them-and-how-to-use-them</link><guid isPermaLink="false">62a803098987675204b216f3</guid><category><![CDATA[FNBRWatch]]></category><category><![CDATA[Fortnite news]]></category><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 04:01:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f4887756dc7d452690ce1469e1a8bb04~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Grappler Gloves are now finally in the game after a little over a week of waiting. Here's exactly where to find them and how you should use them.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f2035ef996da410981cdb08236542b6c~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>Where to find them</h3><p>You will be able to find grappler gloves at different Grapple Stops.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_4978816c8ed344638c338a5fb45477af~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>They can be found all around the map in purple toolboxes. The map below shows the exact locations of the Grapple Stops. The image to the right shows the Grappler Glove icon and the Grappler toolbox icon for extra help.</p>


<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_b2c664bc2aaa43cf8134d16601f5c895~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>How to use them</h3><p>The Grappler Glove is a replacement of the Spider-Man web shooters that were introduced in Chapter 3, Season 1, so they could keep it in both Creative and Battle Royale without having any legal issues. They work exactly the same; however, the cooling is slightly different. </p>

<p>To use them, just aim to the desired location. A string will shoot out and fling you towards that area. Players will be able to swing between different objects for a while however eventually there will be a cooldown. After each swing, you will be required to wait until you can use them again.  Each grappler comes with 40 strings in main modes except competitive modes where they only have 10.</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chapter 3 Season 3 - Season Quest Guides]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some Helpful Guides for the Weekly Zero Point Quests Shortcuts: - Week 1 - Week 2 - Week 3 - Week 4 - Week 5 - Week 6 Week 1 Guides -...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/chapter-3-season-3-season-quest-guides</link><guid isPermaLink="false">629da0005e16283ef21dfe99</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:50:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_a2e7d2bf1da241e5b0af651d1a9ccc35~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Some Helpful Guides for the Weekly Zero Point Quests</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_a2e7d2bf1da241e5b0af651d1a9ccc35~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>Shortcuts:</h3><p><u>- Week 1</u></p>
<p>- Week 2</p>
<p>- Week 3</p>
<p>- Week 4</p>
<p>- Week 5</p>
<p>- Week 6</p><hr><h2>Week 1 Guides</h2><p><a href="https://www.fortniteandmore.com/news/view/how-to-find-and-plant-reality-seeds" target="_top" ><u>- Plant or summon reality saplings using reality seeds</u></a></p>
<p><u>Other Quests do not require guides</u></p><hr><h2>Week 2 Guides</h2><p><a href="https://www.fortniteandmore.com/news/view/how-to-find-and-plant-reality-seeds" target="_blank" >- Q</a>uests will be available shortly</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Unlock the Vibrant Vibin’ Emote Through Twitch Drops]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new "Vibrant Vibin’" emote is now available until June 9th through Twitch Drops. Heres a guide on how to do it from the start. Get your...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/how-to-unlock-the-vibrant-vibin-emote-through-twitch-drops</link><guid isPermaLink="false">629d9ba69a8fd498b214b098</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:22:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_a038f47fd9f14bd8ad649b17473fee56~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A new "Vibrant Vibin’" emote is now available until June 9th through Twitch Drops. Heres a guide on how to do it from the start.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_a038f47fd9f14bd8ad649b17473fee56~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>Get your Twitch account ready & Claim your Reward</h3><p>If you don't already have a <a href="https://www.twitch.tv/" target="_blank" ><u>Twitch</u></a> account create one to complete the steps:</p><ol>
  <li>Connect your Epic Games account to Twitch <a href="https://www.epicgames.com/account/connections#accounts" target="_blank" ><u>here</u></a> </li>
  <li>Watch a Fortnite Stream for 30 minutes (Make sure it has drops enabled by looking in the upper right corner. IF it has drops enabled it will alert you)</li>
  <li>When you are done watching for 30 minutes open the Drop Settings and claim your reward: Start by clicking your user profile > Drops > Claim</li>
  <li>Open Fortnite and you will recive your reward</li>
</ol>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Get the Xbox Dazzle Daggers Axe in Fortnite]]></title><description><![CDATA[A guide on how to get the Dazzle Daggers Pickaxe in Fortnite Chapter 3 Season 3]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/how-to-get-the-xbox-dazzle-daggers-axe-in-fortnite</link><guid isPermaLink="false">629d98c16c5fed6bc0b0b176</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 06:09:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_9f1e3a9d3a884c6b9f537873495de203~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_720,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>NOTE: This will only work until June 21st</p>

<p>Here's a guide on how to get the Free Dazzel Daggers axes in Fortnite</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_9f1e3a9d3a884c6b9f537873495de203~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_720,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>Requirements</h3><p>In order to unlock this reward you much meet the following requirements:
- Have an Xbox/Microsoft account</p>
<p>- Have your Xbox account linked to Fortnite (Find out how to do that)</p>
<p>- Have access to a PC or Mobile Phone</p>
<h3>How to unlock them</h3><p>To unlock the Dazzel Daggers sign into Fortnite over the <a href="https://www.xbox.com/en-US/play?&#38;ef_id=Cj0KCQjwqPGUBhDwARIsANNwjV69GGPJYeI_OkIehx7sqUX3_YG8atupYsLaSLHR3bVVUPIeaWNUTAgaApijEALw_wcB:G:s&#38;OCID=AID2200843_SEM_Cj0KCQjwqPGUBhDwARIsANNwjV69GGPJYeI_OkIehx7sqUX3_YG8atupYsLaSLHR3bVVUPIeaWNUTAgaApijEALw_wcB:G:s&#38;gclid=Cj0KCQjwqPGUBhDwARIsANNwjV69GGPJYeI_OkIehx7sqUX3_YG8atupYsLaSLHR3bVVUPIeaWNUTAgaApijEALw_wcB" target="_blank" ><u>Xbox Cloud gaming services</u></a> on a Mobile Phone or Computer/PC. Once you log in, follow instructions then launch the game. When you launch the game you will be greeted with the free reward</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Upgrade Snap... Here's How to Upgrade the Snap Skin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here's how to Upgrade your Fortnite Battle Pass Exclusive Snap Character. Upgrade and assemble Snap]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/upgrade-snap-here-s-how-to-upgrade-the-snap-skin</link><guid isPermaLink="false">629d930cc77e556372a068a0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 05:59:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_8c42f80f943e48558b3fa5c3ef741b28~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnite Chapter 3 Season 3 Just launched! If you need some help learning how to play the new Season we got you covered. Here's how to upgrade your Snap Battle Pass skin.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_8c42f80f943e48558b3fa5c3ef741b28~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>How to unlock Snap</h3><p>To unlock Snap you first need to own the battle pass. With the battle pass unlocked, you can buy Snap. You will need to have 9 or more Battle stars which can be earned from leveling up by completing quests, missions, and opening supplies around the island.</p>
<h3>Upgrade your Snap Character</h3><p>To Upgrade Snap you need to complete quests to find "Tover Tokens" for Snap. Three Tover Tokens will be placed at separate POIs. TO upgrade snap you need to locate the hidden tokens at each POI. Opening your quest menu will show you what POIs you should look at to find the tokens. </p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_5743c39f7c4d4a2692617df69fbd2dbb~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>TIP: Once you arrive at the POI, look at the minimap to find token icons and locations. </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to Find and Plant Reality Seeds]]></title><description><![CDATA[Heres a step by step guide on how to Find and Plant Reality Seeds for the Fortnite Chapter 3 Season 2 Week 1 challenge]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/how-to-find-and-plant-reality-seeds</link><guid isPermaLink="false">629d3dc0b1a35d5b159f684c</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 05:20:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f7d60c6d38bf4b8e98dd4745e65de3e7~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here's how to complete the Chapter 3 Season 2 Week 1 Challenge where you need to find a reality seed and plant it.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_f7d60c6d38bf4b8e98dd4745e65de3e7~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" title="Credit: @FortniteGame" ></figure><h3>Where to find Reality Seeds</h3><p>To find Reality Seeds you need to head over to the Reality Falls POI on the </p>

<p>west side of the island. On the land outside of the tree, you will find pods. Break the pods and Reality Seeds will appear.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_69ac62c10bbb4ccd878a937057211e5f~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h3>How to Plant the Seeds</h3><p>To plant the reality seeds throw them onto the ground. </p>

<p>NOTE: For this challenge, you need to plant 3 seeds</p>

<h3>VIDEO SHOWCASE</h3><a href="https://video.wixstatic.com/video/ee6e59_3fb31be1e5b94dd7a29dbb9be34d4a7f/1080p/mp4/file.mp4">https://video.wixstatic.com/video/ee6e59_3fb31be1e5b94dd7a29dbb9be34d4a7f/1080p/mp4/file.mp4</a>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Are Tents in Fortnite and How Do You Use Them?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here's what the new "Tents" in Fortnite do and how to use them. Fortnite tents were added recently in Fortnite Chapter 3 - Season 1. This...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/what-are-tents-in-fortnite-and-how-do-you-use-them</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61b151bca783510016bb153a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:51:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_9f6e67a0b5af4009b7c0c580736c040b~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Here's what the new "Tents" in Fortnite do and how to use them.</p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_9f6e67a0b5af4009b7c0c580736c040b~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Fortnite tents were added recently in Fortnite Chapter 3 - Season 1. This new item may look bad but it's actually quite unbelievable. This item allows players to hide, heal, and save. </p>
 <h2>Saving</h2><p>Place any item into the tents with plenty of slots and retrieve them in a future match. This means that any weapon you put in here will save for a future match. When you come back to the placed tent you can get any items you left in there.</p>
<h2>Hide/Heal</h2><p>You can now jump into the tent and "rest" Resting heals your green health bar and can get you back up to 100 while the tent isn't taking any damage. </p>
<h2>Downsides</h2><p>The tent is quite easy to break and it does take storm damage. If your tent is taking damage you cannot rest, pick up, or do anything with it. It will act as a solid object.</p>

<p>View more Chapter 3 Information and guides <a href="https://www.fortniteandmore.com/news/view/fortnite-chapter-3-guides" target="_blank" ><u>here</u></a> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fortnite Sliding | Here is how to slide in Fortnite Chapter 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[Fortnite Chapter 3 has brought so much stuff to the game including a new mechanic - sliding... Here's a guide on how to slide. First off...]]></description><link>https://www.etfn.dev/news/view/fortnite-sliding-heres-how-to-slide-in-fortnite-chapter-3</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61ad1229b7833a0016c359e7</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 19:31:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_298b022c0bc649f0a9d686388bfaaa92~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>ETFN</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fortnite Chapter 3 has brought so much stuff to the game including a new mechanic - sliding... Here's a guide on how to slide.</p>

<p>First off you will need a slope. Find a hill and then press and hold crouch. </p>
 <figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/ee6e59_298b022c0bc649f0a9d686388bfaaa92~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><h2>Sliding on the console. </h2><p>Use the guides below for help.</p>

 <figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/undefined"></figure> ]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>